l gotta hand it to Raj. He found
a really nice spot to have a bachelor party.
(Sheldon:)It's not bad. Unless you compare it
to a train. And then it stinks.
- Are you drinking whiskey?
- lndeed.
(Sheldon:)If I'm to participate in the social convention
that is the stag night...
(Sheldon:)...then I must embrace
all its components...
(Sheldon:)...including tobacco, swear words
and, yes, alcohol.
Jeepers, that's yucky.
(Leonard:)Whoa, it's a little early to start dropping
J- bombs, don't you think?
- Hey, you guys.
- Hey. Nice of you to make it out for Howard.
(Wil:)It was either this or another
hot tub party at George Takei's house.
(Sheldon:)I'm confused.
l thought since our reconciliation...
...l was your friend in this group.
- Oh, I'm friends with Howard too.
- Oh.
l guess you're just friends with anybody.